and a reduction in progression to kidney failure by 43%. The FDA has granted us priority review
for the traditional approval. So I think that just indicates the strength of the Fabhalta data
in IGAN. For Venraphia, we see steady US uptake and growth in a very
competitive way. So we're looking at a lot of the same things that we've seen in the last five years.
So we're looking at a lot of the same things that we've seen in the last five years. So we're looking
very competitive field, I think, as all of you know. That launch is ongoing, we have about 11%
NBRx share. We see a significant market expansion opportunity with most patients still on
supportive care. And as that market grows, we hopeervanrafia will ultimately benefit as a
really effective and safe vascular endothelial agent. And we do expect traditional FDA approval
to drive future growth. You saw in the quarter, we top lined the aligned data. And we do expect
to submit that data,
fda and ema in the first half we will present that data in full and while we didn't reach statistical
significance we feel confident that the data is compelling will allow that full approval to
ultimately happen then moving to slide 13. now rhapsodo is csu launch off to a strong start in
the u.s and we have the early steps now to begin the rollout as well outside outside of the u.s
and i think when you look at the profile we're building pipeline and appeal potential significant
medicine here that could address a range of different dermatology and immunology indications
so starting with the csu launch uh the u.s uh uptake we see 3 000 prescribers to date across
allergists and dermatologists uh now prescribing the medicine 6 000 patients starts and we're
seeing very positive feedback on the speed of the onset of action and we estimate an nbrx share now
of 24 percent which i think is very good in these early phases of launch we are having early access
wins but i would say that access will build over the course of the year so we'll take us the full
year to get to where we want to ultimately get to from an access standpoint and that'll be important
as well because that's what allows us to bridge from free drugs to ultimately paid scripts so
that'll be a steady uh uptake over the course you're not a fast inflection and then outside
of the u.s the china commercial launch uh and the european ec approval that we've received
will enable us to hopefully have a solid launch
in the second half of the year we did also have the positive uh cindu readout uh primary endpoint
in chronic inducible urticaria we saw significantly higher rates of complete responses versus placebo
across all three cindu types first time a medicine has delivered that well tolerated